Veasna Huan

3115 E. Nevada Ave Fresno, CA 93702 www.linkedin.com/pub/veasna-huan/b7/820/b3a (559) 708-8934 veasnahuan@yahoo.com

Summary

Motivated, goal-oriented individual seeking a position where my strong work ethic, abilities, and positive attitude will contribute to the vision of the company. Ten-years of experience providing quality work and strong analytical skills to best meet both companies and customer needs.

Professional Experiences

Rich's Product, Shipping and Receiving/Forklift Operator Fresno, CA

08/2010-11/2013

Managed company inventory using data entry. Handled high volume of products, while communicating daily with customers.

Niacc Technology, Aviation Technician

10/2004-11/2009

Fresno, CA

Conducted routine inspections required by FAA regulations. Repaired and adjusted aircraft systems in a timely manner, increasing customer satisfaction. Routinely conversed with customers to account for their satisfaction and to build lasting relationships through outstanding customer service.

Big 5 Sporting Goods, Customer Service Representative

01/2004-09/2004

Fresno. CA

Controlled inventory, while in training to become manager. Greeted customers and determined customers needs, by familiarizing customers with all aspects of the merchandise. Computed sales and maintained cash and credit payments.

Pizza Hut, Restaurant Manager

01/2000-09/2003

Fresno, CA

High School Diploma

Inspected restaurant to ensure cleanliness. Maintained communication with employees to ensure that that operations ran efficiently. Supervised all aspects of restaurant operations to ensure a well managed environment in which employees thrived and customers were satisfied.

Education

Geekwise Academy, Fresno, CA Fresno County Front-End Web Development Course	2015
Fresno City College, Fresno, CA Police Academy Training (P.O.S.T. certified)	2009
Clovis High School, Clovis, CA	2001

References Available Upon Request